FanQuest Agent turns every World Cup match
into a guided fan journey.
Fans create an identity and connect an Injective testnet wallet,
with a clear review fallback.
They pick a live match, join a quest, and lock winner,
scoring team, and player predictions.
The result resolves in seconds,
calculating points from match data.
An open-box reveal transforms the outcome
into an emotional reward moment.
Points update the leaderboard,
then the fan creates an on-chain claim receipt.
The wallet view separates confirmed proof
from demo reward accounting.
A share-ready X post closes the loop:
predict, compete, reveal, rank, and share.
The Injective EVM testnet transaction
is publicly verifiable in Blockscout.
Status, block, gas, and the FanQuest claim memo
make the journey provable end to end.